<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-03-24T22:16:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Tyu</title><subtitle>长风破浪会有时！
</subtitle><author><name>Your Name</name></author><entry><title type="html">A virtual competition</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/24/a-virtual-competition.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A virtual competition" /><published>2020-03-24T21:53:44+08:00</published><updated>2020-03-24T21:53:44+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/24/a-virtual-competition</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/24/a-virtual-competition.html">&lt;p&gt;I know I am not a ACM material, but I still do…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-virtual-competition&quot;&gt;a virtual competition&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A virtual competition was held in the afternoon, the problems are difficult as ever. I always think they are all just a little more difficult than my ability, but because of this point, I can not work out the problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;number-theory&quot;&gt;number theory&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Number theory is my weekness, such as unique decomposition theorem, Euler theorem, I can not use them skillfully. So I decided to spend more time to study number theory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-novel-coronavious&quot;&gt;the novel coronavious&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The novel voronavious has been out of control, up to now, the number of confirmed patients is 333076, and the number increase 40832 just today! That is a lot more the number of confirmed patients in China. And the global economy has been falling incredibly. I guess the war is coming…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://r.photo.store.qq.com/psc?/V11Be2CB0ZibdZ/gfbE2l9PHUztNHbA2prIH9wzRkSC.ZjWniYlJ01QtFxXNsgiSj58YIi0KJOqpCR37.JDimfyGJ0qIues26OKrvy7kQuyHWOyyRLddzEjeMU!/r&quot; alt=&quot;the novel coronavious&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Your Name</name></author><summary type="html">I know I am not a ACM material, but I still do… a virtual competition A virtual competition was held in the afternoon, the problems are difficult as ever. I always think they are all just a little more difficult than my ability, but because of this point, I can not work out the problems. number theory Number theory is my weekness, such as unique decomposition theorem, Euler theorem, I can not use them skillfully. So I decided to spend more time to study number theory. the novel coronavious The novel voronavious has been out of control, up to now, the number of confirmed patients is 333076, and the number increase 40832 just today! That is a lot more the number of confirmed patients in China. And the global economy has been falling incredibly. I guess the war is coming…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fight with Jekyll and GitHub</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/23/Fight-with-Jekyll-and-GitHub.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fight with Jekyll and GitHub" /><published>2020-03-23T15:13:44+08:00</published><updated>2020-03-23T15:13:44+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/23/Fight-with-Jekyll-and-GitHub</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/23/Fight-with-Jekyll-and-GitHub.html">&lt;p&gt;Today I did nothing, did not study, did not listen to class and did not review what.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;but&quot;&gt;but&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I learned to use Jekyll to set up a blog site, and GitHub’s use!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;an-idea&quot;&gt;an idea&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An idea came to me, although the blog site is set up, it don’t be used to do something, because I usually write blogs at CSDN.After all, CSDN is the technology blog, it can not upload all things, so I decided to write blogs which are not technology blogs at the site, for example diary…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An idea came to me again, I decided to use it as an English diary platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do what you say, so it is why it is here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;today&quot;&gt;today&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today is the first day, I don’t write too much, The so-called”one spirit, then decline,three exhausts”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come on, Oligei!!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Your Name</name></author><summary type="html">Today I did nothing, did not study, did not listen to class and did not review what. but But I learned to use Jekyll to set up a blog site, and GitHub’s use! an idea An idea came to me, although the blog site is set up, it don’t be used to do something, because I usually write blogs at CSDN.After all, CSDN is the technology blog, it can not upload all things, so I decided to write blogs which are not technology blogs at the site, for example diary… An idea came to me again, I decided to use it as an English diary platform. Do what you say, so it is why it is here. today Today is the first day, I don’t write too much, The so-called”one spirit, then decline,three exhausts”. Come on, Oligei!!</summary></entry></feed>